It's okay, let's move on
In the night of the night,
the clouds are coming
The clouds are coming, and
look at the light of the sky
If we see the moon,
we'll see the moon We'll
see the moon in the future
So I'll
take
this time to
explain how the race works.
The course consists of one lap
around Long Ring Long Land.
It may sound easy, but
believe me, it's not.
If your boat sinks, your team is
immediately disqualified from the race.
Oh, yeah! Weapons?
They're allowed!
Guns, cannons, explosives,
anything you can think of!
If that sounds unfair, then you've got no
right at all to call yourself a pirate!
Go, Portia!
Yeah, drown that long
nose! Who, me? That's it!
We have to win this now!
Drowning is fair play.
It's in the rules.
I'm excited about this! What?
about losing.
Now pay close attention, Usopp.
If anything happens to those
two ladies, I'll eviscerate you.
We are going to win this race.
I know it.
Wow, they think they
have a chance of winning.
Let the fools think whatever
they want to think, Porcha.
We'll sink them right off the bat.
Right, Monda?
Hey, fool!
Fool!
He honestly thinks they're going to win.
What a riot.
No one's ever beat the Foxy Pirates.
I doubt this race will
even last five minutes.
Am I right?
You know it.
To ensure you don't get lost, we're
providing each team with an eternal pose.
Get lost?
What's this doofus talking about?
Why would we leave the island?
We're taking the inside
track the whole way.
I'm afraid it won't be that simple.
Now, on your marks, Jeopardy!
Just tell me why it won't be simple.
Trust me.
Tell me why.
I've got a terrible feeling about this!
No, quit babbling and tell us why already!
Push, push, push!
Time to reveal the secret of our book.
It's got a sneaky little burpee.
Oh, no!
We didn't get far enough!
What's the big deal?
It's just a barrel.
No, not me! Don't!
And they've been released!
Look at that!
Kaboom!
The old barrel mines!
The Coaster's Chump Card!
See you later, chumps!
You're supposed to avoid
thinking, you know!
Wish us good luck!
All right, Capote, give them a
taste of your fishman karate. Yeah!
Surface Splitter!
The boat's breaking apart!
Our balance!
We've got to stay balanced!
Take this! Eat flame!
No thanks.
All right. Ocho flue.
What the? Capote!
And now, flip.
Perfect! Now's our chance!
Usopp, jump in the
water and pull the boat!
Hurry!
Are you crazy?!
Khaboudi, Monda, get it together!
Come on, pedal!
I think it's about time that
we get to work, Hamburg.
Really?
Oh, boy, I was hoping you'd say that.
All right, folks,
currently in the lead of the race is
everyone's all-time favorite, the Cutie Wagon.
Right behind them in second
place is the Barry Tyler.
Hey, wait a sec.
Why don't we just use one of your dials?
Oh, good idea.
We can give this breath dial a shot.
We were going faster before.
Well, do you have a jet dial on you?
Come on, you know how rare those are.
We're talking about losing a crew member.
He's right.
We can't lose here.
There's just too much at stake.
If we lose, I know they'll
definitely take me first.
I just know it.
Oh, why?
Why am I so cute?
Whatever.
You just keep on dreaming.
Robin, this isn't the
best time for reading.
I'm rowing, too.
Well, yeah, your hands are, but
you're not really focused on it.
Right, Robin.
You don't want to end up like me, right?
Better work hard.
I am working hard.
Yeah, working hard in archaeology.
What do you think?
Should we head for the finish line,
or should we enjoy seeking them first?
I enjoy casually scrolling through the
finish line as much as the next guy,
but I want to make that chick suffer.
Simply winning this thing ain't
going to be enough for me anymore.
What the?
How's this work for you?
Excellent, Robert.
That is downright cheating.
Let go.
It's too bad they already noticed.
Capote, no.
They're going to pay.
Let's just keep paddling with all we got.
We've got to try and catch up to them
before they get an even bigger lead on us.
Well then, I guess I'll be
seeking them after all. Oh.
Hm?
They're now approaching the most
fearsome obstacles of the course,
the Long Coral Reef.
And just beyond that
foreboding and difficult patch
is the dreaded Long Ring
Whirlpool of Long King.
Can they overcome these hurdles?
And oh, we'll all be.
What now?
Talk about unexpected.
It's Full Dash Hamburg at full speed.
And riding atop him is the
master of obstruction himself.
the scourge of fairness, and the
greatest scoundrel of all time, our boss,
Silver Fox Foxy!
It's him!
I've just come up with an evil idea.
This race is really heating up.
The next course obstacle, the
long coral reef is dead ahead,
leading the race is Portia
and the cutie wagon.
Look, that weird reef is causing
some unusual currents to form.
Going in blind is not a good idea.
Ugh, I can't believe this stupid
race has lasted this long.
We're counting on you, Monda. Yeah!
And don't forget,
there's someone on land looking for
every opportunity to sabotage this race.
Our boss, Silver Fox Foxy.
Just what does he have in store for us?
All right, hope you like fish and noodles,
free of charge. For real? Oh, how cool.
Thank you.
Why is it that all the good cooks
like you were already taken?
Your curly-cute eyebrows are so cute.
You know, I gotta say, I won't
mind if I get Davey back.
Hey, we need another
round of drinks down here.
The brew is endless,
so drink all you want.
Thanks, you guys are all right.
Yeah, get him, boss.
It's only a matter of time.
Wait, wait, what's this?
Come on, Nami, keep
rowing. Not yet. Not yet!
They're getting further ahead of us!
I know, okay?
We're not going in yet!
The Cutie Wagon takes
advantage of this opportunity
and plunges forward into
the long coral reef!
Let's go, Monda! Sure!
Hey, wait a minute! What's happening?
Monda!
Uh-oh, they came back. What?!
The Cutie Wagon has been
pushed back out of the reef!
What's happening down there?!
I don't understand!
See, I knew there was something
weird about those currents.
Now!
Let's get moving, Usopp!
Right!
Let's try this again, Monda!
Come on, this way!
Hey! What's that?
Ha-ha!
And there you have it!
The devilish interference
we've all been waiting for!
Some kind of smokescreen!
Now the reef will be far too dangerous!
And there you have it!
Operation Whiteout successful!
Let's see how you navigate through this
reef when you can't even see through it!
You're sure it worked?
What the hell?!
They made it through
with no trouble at all!
How is that possible?!
I called it.
What about the duty wagon?
Oh no!
Seems they've been pushed back again!
Hey, the boat is moving on its own!
What's going on here, Nami?
This place is a maze
of currents. Currents?
Right.
That giant whirlpool
ahead of us is causing
smaller whirlpools to
form within the reef?
resulting in these strange currents.
Doesn't matter if we can't
see, their course won't change.
As long as we take the right entrance,
these currents will guide the
boat along all by themselves.
Incredible!
You're a miracle!
That's what you can do when you've got the
best navigator on the
Grand Line in your crew!
Take that!
Damn it!
But they won't be celebrating for long.
Once they're out of the reef, they
head straight into the long ring.
Usopp, stop freaking out
and use it. Use what?
The impact dial.
But I don't have it with me, though.
Yeah, then what's this?
What's that?
We're dead. How did you?
Come on, hurry.
If you don't use it soon, we'll be
sucked down into the giant whirlpool.
You know what it's like to use that thing?
Come on, we're running out of time here.
So that's why you've
been acting so calm, huh?
You had this plan from the
very beginning, didn't you?
Well...
Oh!
The Barrel Tiger picked
up some tremendous speed!
They're not just going
faster, they're playing!
And with that move, the Barrel
Tiger now has a commanding lead!
Does this mean defeat
for the Beauty Wagon?
We were way too easy on them!
I'm counting on you!
Karoo, time!
Two fish engines!
They're not out of the race yet!
By fusing fish man muscle
with the fin of a shark,
the cutie wagon has
doubled its engine speed!
They're blazing through the
coral and closing the gap!
The race is now half over!
Meanwhile, the barrel tiger
desperately paddles on!
Usopp, wake up!
Ugh, where am I?
Get off and start paddling!
Your arm seems to be
bending the wrong way.
What is that?
Looks like a course marker.
Turn right, huh?
Guess we'll turn right then.
What's this?
She broke it.
Our boss is Ploy Number 18.
Operation Life has failed.
What a formidable woman.
Does she not believe in
anything in this world?
She's fell mouth.
Too the race continues with the barrel
tiger maintaining its strong lead.
What are these columns of water?
They are now clearing the long
waves that reach high into?
The sky was that supposed to be natural?
Oh grandma.
Oh boss, I mean oh grandma.
Ah, baby.
My time on this earth is over.
The boss unleashes his third nasty trick.
Hey you!
A dying granny over here.
Won't you stop and help me?
Unbelievable.
She completely ignores.
a child and his sick,
helpless grandmother.
The only thing she cares about
is getting what she wants.
How cold-hearted.
The Ice Queen Navigator Nami.
I told you to can it.
I'd never fall for a
ridiculous trick like that.
Did I mention she was found out? Huh?
Hey, look.
It's the finish line.
This race will soon be decided.
Not so fast.
It's not gonna be that easy.
The cutie wagon is closing in quickly.
These are the final moments of round one's
donut race who will win
i told you these lame
tricks won't work she even sees through
operation fake gold
formidable truly formidable
and now i have a question for her what is
it like to go through
life so dated piss off
it's too late for her her heart is cold she
has no soul But the real goal is nearby.
We're getting close.
I'm not using that dial again.
Yeah, yeah, I know.
Meanwhile, Portia and the cutie wagon
have tragically stopped at the fake goal.
What's going on?
Who won the race?
What the...
Where did everybody go?
The purity of your heart is astounding.
Pay attention, Portia.
You've been tricked.
Those guys are complete idiots.
I'd die of embarrassment
if we lost to them.
They'd take one of our crew, too.
That's worse.
Oh, no!
This doll is a complete fake! What?
Who would do something so evil?
The barrel tiger is finally
approaching the long bamboo cape.
The goal is just beyond it.
They're in the homestretch.
Hey, he's right.
I can see the finish line. Wait up!
But they're catching up to us.
There's no way we'll
beat them at this speed.
I've got an idea.
Usak, can you shoot down that bamboo?
Bamboo? All right.
Like that?
Yes, more, more! Monja! Capote!
Move it! Full speed ahead!
We'll ram them and sink that stupid
boat to the bottom of the ocean!
Whoa! Bingo!
Oh, no!
Capote, you say something!
I've had it!
They're gonna pay for this!
Cutie button!
What's that?
Some kind of magic flower trick?
Flower!
Chicken!
Oh, flower shitting it.
Hey, look out!
Oh, no.
Looks like we sprung a lake.
Don't worry.
We can make it.
We're almost to the goal.
Keep paddling.
Round one of the Davy back fight, the
donut race, is about to come to a close.
Oh, Murchin. Come on.
Stay strong, Monda.
We can't let him beat us.
We're going to lose if
we don't do something.
Bring us up alongside him.
Right, boss.
Robin, baby!
Nami, my darling, you look so
hot when you're going fast!
Man, you guys almost
won. What do you mean?
We're totally going to win.
Not so fast.
Take a look over there.
Our boss is coming. Yeah?
So what? What can he do?
Our boss is just like you.
He has Devil Fruit powers.
Slow, slow beam!
And the winner is the cutie wagon.
The hero of the first round of the
Davey Back fight Is our very own idol.
Way to go!
Thank you.
You are the greatest.
Looks like we're about
to get a new crew member.
There's nobody that can
beat the Foxy Pirates.
We always win.
Oh, oh, oh.
Hoy, hoy, hoy, hoy.
Befefefefefefe.
Now it's time for you guys to play up.
We are taking one of your crew.
You guys hurt?
Is everybody OK, Robert?
Yes, we're all right.
What the heck happened out there?
I'd like to know the same thing.
We'd all like to know what happened.
Did we really lose somehow?
You looked like you were going to win,
but then you suddenly slowed down?
and they passed you.
There's nothing strange about that.
It was caused by slow-mo photon.
Hey, what did you do to
Nami's team, you smug bastard?
What's a slow-mo photon?
They are particles unlike any
others known to modern science.
Whatever this light touches,
be it an animal, a liquid, a solid, or
even a gas, will lose a fixed amount
of its velocity, while
simultaneously retaining?
all its other energy. You're dumb.
That makes no sense at all.
He just bugged me.
Oh, so you OK?
No way.
Something that ridiculous
is just - Impossible?
Is that what you're thinking?
Surely you know that such a naive,
childish claim has no merit
out here on these waters.
Everything they touch slows down.
That's the power of slow-mo photons.
Now that makes sense.
Why didn't you say so before?
After I ate the slow, slow fruit, I became
a slow motion man, capable of producing?
these particles from my body. Observe!
Ah!
A floating cannonball!
The slow, slow beam!
The effect lasts approximately 30 seconds,
after which the object will
regain its original speed?
as if nothing had ever happened.
Can't believe your eyes, I take it.
Oh, no!
I get it.
So that's why we didn't win the race.
It also explains why they're so
overly confident about these games.
What a joke of a Devil Fruit power.
It doesn't matter!
You guys lost!
You know all the rules and
you agree to all the terms!
The donut race is over!
And we are the winners!
Aw, too bad for you guys.
That concludes round one.
And now we shall commence with
the awarding of the prize.
The winning captain will select
a member of the opposing crew.
You...
My first selection is none other than...
You, the doctor, Tonitoni Chopper!
Ha?
Bring him to me at once!
No, no! No!
No!
Chopper!
Such a rare creature.
You're even softer than
I imagined you'd be.
Trust me, I hold him, too.
He's just so damn cute, and he's ours now.
Chopper!
So that creep had his
eyes set on Chopper, huh?
Well, I suppose that he is among
the rarest of rare animals.
Or maybe he collects cute things?
You know, I wouldn't
rule out a fur fetish.
Why does it even matter?
Focus, people!
That freak over there
just took our friend!
You guys.
All right, Dr.
Chopper, enough of all that.
You're one of my crew now.
You need to pledge your loyalty to me.
And you can start by putting on this mask.
You guys.
I'm so sorry that we lost Chopper.
We did our best.
Farewell.
He is truly a rarity.
I'm here, you're talking reindeer.
He's so amazing.
We're going to get along great.
Here.
Welcome aboard!
You guys!
Listen!
I only went out to sea because of you!
I won't! No! I refuse!
Luffy, you invited me!
I said sail to be one of the Straw Hats!
I won't go with them! Please! No!
I am the ship's doctor
of the Straw Hat Pirates!
Doty-doty Chopper!
I won't go!
Quit your bellyaching, Chopper.
It's disgraceful.
Uh, Zoro?
You made the choice to set
sail as a pirate. Only you.
And now you have to live with the
consequences of that decision.
We agreed to the terms of this game.
You, Usopp, and everyone
else did the best they could.
But not one pirate worth his salt is
going to sympathize with those tears.
A man would suck it up and quietly
watch the rest of this game.
What's wrong with you?
Don't you know how he must be feeling?
Boil me or cook me alive!
Give me your worst, you bastard!
Chopper.
That boy.
Whoa, that swordsman is totally awesome!
All right, you teach him a lesson, Zoro!
Yeah, get Chopper back!
Hey, boss, let's take him next.
That reindeer's got guns.
Let's get the second event started.
So inspirational, I can't stop crying.
Yeah, we still have two
rounds left of this.
There's no way we're letting these
jerks take our emergency food supply.
Saji, we're counting on you!
The exchange is complete
and the excitement
explodes as the daily
backbite enters round two.
Hey, wasn't Chopper supposed
to be in the second round?
How can he compete if they took him?
Good point.
That's one of the most
thrilling parts of the game.
Remember the rules.
You cannot change your team's roster.
No replacements allowed. In other words,
only the remaining two contestants
can participate in round two's game,
the groggy ring.
This gives the foxy
team an early advantage.
What?
That's not fair.
Actually, you could sit this one out, too.
Nah, but feel free to do
the same thing, you loser.
It's hard to believe that they're
going to work together as a team.
What was that? Knock it off!
I will now explain the
rules of the groggy ring.
We have a playing field,
and we have two goals.
Knock the ball into the goal, and you win.
However, the ball isn't actually a ball.
The balls are people.
Both teams must select
someone to be the ball.
Make your selection.
You heard him.
Which one of you two guys
is going to be the ball?
Ballmarker.
Who said you get to pick?
You're the ball, you moss-headed bastard.
Oh, there it is.
Their entrance theme song.
it's time to welcome back the
undisputed elites of the groggy
race they are undefeated unbeatable
unstoppable yeah crush them the
famous groggy monsters have taken
the field behold the kings of the
ring first up is full dash hamburger
following behind is taco machine
And last but not least, the half-giant,
half-fish-man himself, Big Pan the Optown!
This is literally a monstrous march!
What is that?
That fish-man is ginormous! Oh, crap!
He's the one wearing the
ball marker! Fish-fish!
You'll never beat him!
Disappointed?
Not at all.